<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="treetracker">Treetracker</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="your_note">Suas notas</string>
    <string name="remove_photo">Remover foto</string>
    <string name="tree_height_save_error" translatable="false">Por favor, tente novamente</string>
    <string name="tree_height_title">Altura da árvore</string>

    <string name="cancel">Cancelar</string>
    <string name="save">Salvar</string>
    <string name="mark_gps">Marcar posição GPS</string>

    <string name="password">Senha</string>
    <string name="organization">Organização</string>

    <string name="gps_location_assessment">Avaliando a localização</string>
    <string name="enable_location_access">Permitir o acesso a localização</string>
    <string name="you_must_enable_location_access_in_your_settings_in_order_to_continue">Você deve permitir o acesso a localização para continuar!</string>

    <string name="location_permission_alert_title">Permitir que Treetracker acesse sua localização?</string>
    <string name="location_permission_alert_message">Por favor, abra as Configurações do seu dispositivo e permita acesso ao local para o Treetracker</string>

    <string name="change_language">Alterar idioma</string>
    <string name="language">Idioma</string>
    <string name="stop">Parar</string>
    <string name="add_tree">ADICIONAR ÁRVORE</string>

    <!--Strings add for fragment_new_tree.xml-->
    <string name="tree">árvore</string>

    <string name="sync_blocked" translatable="false">Sincronização bloqueada</string>
    <string name="sync_started">Sincronização iniciada</string>
    <string name="sync_preparing">Preparando a sincronização</string>
    <string name="sync_stopped">Sincronização interrompida</string>
    <string name="nothing_to_sync">Sem dados para sincronizar</string>
    <string name="sync_failed">A sincronização falhou! Por favor, tente novamente</string>
    <string name="sync_successful">Sincronização concluída com sucesso!</string>
    <string name="tree_saved" translatable="false">Árvore salva</string>
    <string name="next" translatable="false">Próximo</string>
    <string name="back" translatable="false">Voltar</string>

    <!--Strings for the Login fragment-->
    <string name="greenstand_welcome_text" translatable="false"><b>Greenstand Treetracker</b></string>
    <string name="phone_text_hint" translatable="false">Número do telefone</string>
    <string name="email_text_hint" translatable="false">Ou endereço de e-mail</string>
    <string name="login_button_title" translatable="false">CONECTAR</string>
    <string name="signup_button_titile" translatable="false">INSCREVER-SE</string>
    <string name="first_name_hint" translatable="false">Nome</string>
    <string name="last_name_hint" translatable="false">Sobrenome</string>
    <string name="organization_text_hint" translatable="false">Organização (opcional)</string>
    <string name="email_placeholder">E-mail</string>
    <string name="phone_placeholder">Telefone</string>
    <string name="name_placeholder">Nome</string>

    <string name="storagePermissQuestion" translatable="false">Permitir que <b>Treetracker</b> armazene dados em seu dispositivo?</string>
    <string name="locationPermissionQuestion" translatable="false">Permitir que <b>Treetracker</b> acesse a sua localização?</string>
    <string name="cameraPermissionQuestion" translatable="false">Permitir que <b>Treetracker</b> acesse a câmera?</string>
    <string name="storage_permission_title" translatable="false"><b>Permissão de armazenamento</b></string>
    <string name="location_permission_title" translatable="false"><b>Permissão da localização</b></string>
    <string name="camera_permission_title" translatable="false"><b>Permissão da câmera</b></string>

    <string name="focus_warning">Detectamos que a foto não está nítida o suficiente.
        \n Por favor, pressione o botão voltar e tire uma nova foto, se necessário.</string>
    <string name="organization_pre_fill" translatable="false">""</string>

    <string name="syncing" translatable="false">Sincronizando...</string>
    <string name="uploading_trees" translatable="false">Enviando árvores</string>
    <string name="admin_password" translatable="false">Senha do administrador</string>
    <string name="config_parameters" translatable="false">Parâmetros de configuração</string>
    <string name="location_data_config" translatable="false">Parâmetros de configuração dos dados de localização</string>
    <string name="min_time_btwn_updates" translatable="false">Tempo mínimo entre atualizações</string>
    <string name="min_distance_between_updates" translatable="false">Distância mínima entre atualizações</string>
    <string name="convergence_timeout" translatable="false">Tempo limite de convergência</string>
    <string name="convergence_timeout_hint" translatable="false">Tempo limite de convergência em milissegundos</string>
    <string name="convergence_data_size" translatable="false">Tamanho dos dados de convergência</string>
    <string name="convergence_data_size_hint" translatable="false">Tamanho dos dados de convergência necessário</string>
    <string name="lon_std_dev_threshold" translatable="false">Limite do desvio padrão para a Longitude</string>
    <string name="lat_std_dev_threshold" translatable="false">Limite do desvio padrão para a Latitude</string>
    <string name="add_note_to_tree">Adicionar notas sobre a árvore</string>
    <string name="note">NOTAS</string>

    <!--Strings for the permission management and rationale-->
    <string name="accept_camera_permission_header">Permitir acesso a câmera</string>
    <string name="accept_camera_permission_message">Este aplicativo precisa de acesso a câmera. Aceite esta permissão para usar este dispositivo para tirar fotos</string>
    <string name="accept_permission">Aceitar permissão</string>
    <string name="accept_location_permission_header">Aceitar pemissão de localização</string>
    <string name="accept_location_permission_message">Este aplicativo precisa de acesso a localização para obter a posição das árvores. Aceite esta permissão para usar o recurso de localizar árvores</string>
    <string name="open_settings_header">Aceitar permissões</string>
    <string name="open_settings_message">Você recusou estas permissões anteriormente e terá que acessar as configurações do aplicativo para permiti-las. Clique abaixo em abrir configurações para aceitar as permissões necessárias.</string>
    <string name="open_settings">Abrir Configurações</string>
    <string name="user_exists_header">Usuário já existe</string>
    <string name="user_exists_message">Por favor, clique no seu perfil para continuar com esta conta de plantador</string>

    <string name="poor_gps_message">Sua conexão GPS está fraca.\n Tente os passos abaixo:\n 1. Certifique-se que você não está em um local fechado.\n 2. Acesse Configurações > Localização > Modo de Origem e escolha Alta Acurácia.\n 3. O sinal GPS é mais forte em espaços abertos. Se você está em um local fechado, você terá um sinal GPS ruim.</string>
    <string name="poor_gps_header">A obtenção da localização da árvore falhou</string>
    <string name="upload">ENVIO</string>
    <string name="messages">MENSAGENS</string>
    <string name="track">LOCALIZAR</string>
    <string name="viewLiveWebMap">ver o Web Map em tempo real!</string>
    <string name="click_on">Clique em</string>
    <string name="tracking_instruction">Tirar sua árvore para rastreamento.</string>
    <string name="selfie_instruction">Para tirar uma selfie e continuar seu cadastro.</string>
    <string name="recapture_tutorial">Clique no botão para capturar a árvore novamente.</string>
    <string name="capture_tutorial">CLique no botão para salvar esta árvore.</string>
    <string name="phone_validation_error">Número de telefone inválido. O número deve ter no mínimo 7 digitos e no máximo e 15 digitos</string>
    <string name="email_validation_error">E-mail inválido. O endereço de e-mail deve ter o símbolo @</string>
    <string name="tree_capture_review_text">Clique no botão para adicionar notas.</string>
    <string name="survey">Pesquisa</string>
    <string name="message">Mensagem</string>
    <string name="policy_text_blob">
How We Handle Data:
        \n
Our primary goals are to use data to create a greener earth and offer an option for economic opportunity in areas of extreme poverty. We believe that the scientific and project related data we collect (that is not private by nature) should be freely available to the public. Unless otherwise authorized we will not disclose sensitive user information, such as contact information. Our primary data collection is focused around scientific research and creating a transparent system to collect field data related to the survival processes of trees as well as any information related to the systematic harvesting of tree related products. This information includes planter geo-tagged, time-stamped photos and other user entered data.
        \n
By using our services, you are agreeing to allow us to use your environmentally related information and make it publicly accessible via websites. User’s first name and/or organization name may be displayed with the corresponding tree data. With prior consent, other user related information may be displayed. Upon request all user data may be hidden from public view. Phone numbers and/or email addresses may be used by GreenStand to contact planters, but will not be shared with third parties without prior consent.
        \n
        \n
Project Related/Scientific Data:
        \n
GreenStand upholds an open scientific data policy and intends to make any scientific finding, that may positively affect the environment and/or social welfare, freely available. Using data we receive through user inputs on our mobile applications, website and database systems, we intended to identify problems, solutions and trends in environmental/social health. By using our services and software, you are thereby agreeing to allow us to publicly display project related data and scientific findings. In the event that data collected with this software is sensitive, please contact us at Info@greenstand.org so that we may act accordingly.
        \n
        \n
How We Collect Data:
        \n
Mobile Applications:
        \n
Photos: time-stamped, Geo-tagged.
        \n
User entered information: name, email address, organization name, phone number, field notes.
        \n
App settings for users
        \n
Application analytics: software crash reports, phone make and model.
        \n
Website Application: Database entries, general analytics.
        \n
Donor supplied information
        \n
        \n
User Data We Collect:
        \n
Information relating to individual users or organizations will not be disclosed without prior consent. We are handling all user related data (full name, phone numbers, email) securely using modern cryptography. Planter’s full names and contact information will never be shared without prior consent.
        \n
Personal Information: On our tree tracker app we require a name, and email, and optionally a phone number and an organization name. All personal data is stored in a secure database.
        \n
Mobile App users: Our mobile apps collect the following personal information: User entered information: name, email address, organization name, phone number.
        \n
Donor information: When you make a donation we collect information that is used solely for accounting, tax reporting and donation processing purposes. This information is guarded with utmost care and will not be sold, shared or traded with any other entity. We do abide by IRS requirement to disclose limited information that is mandated to be available on public taxes records. Donor information may also be disclosed at the donor\'s request. We collect the following donor information: name, address, amount of donation, any other personal information given to us.
        \n
User Photos:
        \n
GreenStand’s tree tracking program runs on the collection of time-stamped, geotagged photos. This information is stored in a secure database from which it is displayed in the form of a tree map. We also use this information to generate statistics related to tree planting. We are only interested in tree-related photos, please don’t send us anything else. With the proper use of this system, all photo taken will relate to environmental data and GreenStand does not consider or treat uploaded photos as “user data.” By using our mobile application you are agreeing to allow us to use your photos.
        \n
        \n
User Data Deletion:
To request your data be deleted, contact Info@greenstand.org . Note, the complete removal of all personal data is only possible before tree capture data tokenization.
        \n
        \n
Changes to the Policy
        \n
It is our intent to hold the principles of this policy, but we do understand there may be a need to change it from time to time. Changes will be posted on our website as soon as possible.
        \n
        \n
© 2022 GreenStand (registered 501(c)3 nonprofit. EIN: 47-3150283 ). Info@greenstand.org
        \n
Privacy Policy
    </string>
    <string name="announcement">Aviso</string>
    <string name="click_to_write_message">Clique para escrever uma mensagem</string>
    <string name="no_internet_header">Sem conexão com a internet</string>
    <string name="no_internet_content">Por favor, conecte-se a uma rede Wi-fi ou habilite os dados móveis para acessar este link</string>
    <string name="tracking_progress_header">Rastreamento em andamento</string>
    <string name="tracking_progress_message">Não mova o telefone até que o rastreamento seja concluído</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Política de Privacidade</string>

</resources>